[
	{
		"question":"krzyczeć",
		"answers":["cry", "shout", "scream"]
	},
	{
		"question":"śmierć",
		"answers":["death", "passing", "quietus"]
	},
	{
		"question":"ból",
		"answers":["pain", "sore", "ache", "hurt"]
	},
	{
		"question":"tortura",
		"answers":["torture", "torment"]
	},
	{
		"question":"krew",
		"answers":["blood"]
	},
	{
		"question":"masakra",
		"answers":["massacre", "carnage", "butchery"]
	},
	{
		"question":"dręczyć",
		"answers":["torment", "rack", "bother"]
	},
	{
		"question":"koszmar",
		"answers":["nightmare", "incubus"]
	},
	{
		"question":"żałoba",
		"answers":["mourning", "bereavement"]
	},
	{
		"question":"porzucić",
		"answers":["abandon", "desert", "leave"]
	}
]